[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Whoopi Goldberg voice in the 1998 animated movie The Rugrats Movie?", "correct_answer": "Ranger Margaret", "incorrect_answers": ["Reptar Wagon", "Nurse", "Lt. Klavin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is believed that this was the smallest dinosaur.", "correct_answer": "Compsognathus", "incorrect_answers": ["Brachiosaurus", "Amphicoelias", "Argentinasaurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word is commonly used to refer to the central area of the tornado?", "correct_answer": "Eye", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Heart", "Navel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A clay tablet, which dates from around 2300 bce is on display at the museum in Konya, Turkey. What is on the tablet?", "correct_answer": "The earliest known map", "incorrect_answers": ["The earliest known math text.", "The earliest known accounting ledger.", "The earliest known portrait."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before 2008 a female had not attained the rank of a 4-Star General in U.S. history.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who are the founders of Popeyes Chicken  Biscuits?", "correct_answer": "Al Copeland and Jerome Pentsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Al Pentsky and Jerome Copeland", "John Wright and Johnny Capowski", "John Capowski and Johhny Wright"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie, which featured The Stay Puft Marshmallow Man, sparked the catchphrase Who you gonna call??", "correct_answer": "Ghost busters", "incorrect_answers": ["Poltergeist", "The Exorcist", "Poltergeist II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does carcinology study?", "correct_answer": "Crustaceans", "incorrect_answers": ["Malignant tumors in animals and humans", "The outer shells of invertebrates and reptiles", "Crabs, lobsters, and crayfish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are different types of massage. Approximately how many?", "correct_answer": "More than 150", "incorrect_answers": ["More than 50", "More than 20", "More than 300"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Ricks cafe in the movie classic, Casablanca?", "correct_answer": "Ricks Cafe American", "incorrect_answers": ["Ricks", "The Red Parrot", "Rick and Sams Cafe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Ferdinand Marcos", "incorrect_answers": ["Ramon Magsaysay", "Sergio Osme\u00f1a Sr.", "Elpidio Quirino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which gland of the human body can Hurthle cells be found?", "correct_answer": "Thyroid gland", "incorrect_answers": ["Thymus gland", "Adrenal gland", "Pituitary gland"]}]